Tina Camacho

Experienced Registered and Certified Pharmacy Technician

To obtain a full-time position in a Pharmacy setting as a Registered and Certified pharmacy technician. I have worked as a pharmacy technician for almost 10 years and enjoy it immensely. I am a self-motivator, a self-starter, and am able to well under pressure. I would be a great asset to any company that is looking for a loyal and dedicated worker.

Work Experience

Pharmacy Technician

University Health System - San Antonio, TX

February 2003 to July 2010

Customer Service, assist pharmacists in labeling and filling prescriptions, assist patients in dropping off and picking up prescriptions, entering prescriptions into computer, running a register, pre-packaging bulk medications, packaging of mail-order prescriptions, medication ordering, screening calls for pharmacists, calling Dr's to clarify prescriptions, work with Medicaid and Medicare on prescription coverage and refill authority, maintaining a clean and productive working environment, verifying that patients receives correct medications, scan prescriptions

Cashier then Pharmacy Technician

HEB - San Antonio, TX

June 1999 to February 2003

Entered prescriptions into computer, assisted customers in dropping off and picking up medications, called and faxed Dr's requesting refills, assembled prescriptions, called insurance companies to verify coverage and get approval, worked the register, customer service, placed medication orders through Cardinal and other drug order companies, put Rx's in numerical order in books, maintained a clean and productive working environment

Education

Diploma in Communications and Multilingua,I

Brackenridge HS - San Antonio, TX

1996 to 2000

Certifications

Texas State Board of Pharmacy

April 2004 to June 2011

Texas Registered Pharmacy Technician

Pharmacy Technician Certification Board

December 2000 to November 2011

Nationally Certified Pharmacy Technician